<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[The Road of Voice]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[The Road of Voice]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/roadofvoice/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 10:49:15 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/roadofvoice/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 10:49:14 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Darkness ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/16b46ffe-07cb-4652-94fa-9fba3d3b5327.jpg">,<h1>Darkness </h1>,<p>In the darkness I am awakened by the quick patter of footsteps across the living room. I recognize the sound of little feet, now muted on the carpet up the stairs. The boy slips beneath the heavy covers with rapid heart and breath. </p>,<p>“A bad dream,” he whispers, and a pause. </p>,<p>“I dreamed my pinkys fell off.”</p>,<p>Shadows and scales of the underbelly. Seed sprouts at depth cannot ascend the stairs to reach the light and silently wither beneath the darkness. </p>,<p>It is  late We’ve gathered to see the children acting out a ritual, a festival, a play— abstract and forgotten, foreign to many. The message is simple. Dark and sinister forces lurk, a dragon perhaps. Our decency, civility, and goodness have been taken for granted. It was not always this way and like a bad habit can return Not always choice and were not always in the</p>,<p>The boy climbed into my bed and slept the whole night through. In the gathering grey of early morning, we silently stared at the ceiling and enjoyed the warmth beneath the covers. The boy turned to me and said, in a hushed voice, “Last night, I dreamed that I was a light bulb.”</p>,<p>In the park on a wide green lawn sit parents gathered for Michaelmas. The bright sunshine of the day betrays us. Gathered with one another, friends new and old, the meaning forgotten, many choose instead to chatter amongst their bread and spread. </p>,<p>Walking with a veil unlifted I go<br>As I sing songs to the earth,<br>Walking with a veil unlifted I go, <br>As <br>Mighty is my courage, mighty is my strength,<br>Mighty is my courage, yes, mighty is my strength. </p>,<p>The beat of the deep drum is a slow reverberation, a steady reminder. Recall the silk and grey, the running and the flowing of the darkness that pervades our world, in shapes and forms forgotten. These times, so dark, the children unaware of what they have not unleashed.</p>,<p>Project hope. Embody hope. Children are </p>,<p>It i</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/roadofvoice/the-bright-sunshine-of-the-day-betrays-us-the-children-act/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2b1bdbe8-2885-42b7-b5b3-015a64a90027</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 07:45:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lao-Tzu in Exile]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/8faccdc9-74a5-43e1-bb08-ca9fc484a65c.jpg"><h1>Lao-Tzu in Exile</h1><p>After reading &quot;Trying Not to Try&quot; I have fresh eyes for Lau-Tzu poems. </p></article>,<p>At last I’ve chosen water as my boat,<br>Here where jackal’s cries grind down the moon. <br>The way of heaven is an empty road.<br>Our names are paper ships: they do not float<br>For long. Success is a great misfortune.<br>At last I’ve chosen water as my boat.<br>The Emperor’s court was an ill-fitting coat;<br>It was men shouting in a crowded room. <br>The way of heaven is an empty road<br>Vanishing in darkness. The leaves of oaks <br>Can never fall too late or too soon.<br>At last I’ve chosen water as my boat<br>For it returns to the sea, as a bell’s note<br>Fades into the echoing air of noon. <br>The way of heaven is this empty road<br>Which I walk. A single strand of smoke;<br>Stars shimmering above endless dunes.<br>At last I’ve chosen water as my boat.<br>The way of heaven is an empty road.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.jayleeming.com/lao-tzu-in-exile.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">60ff7761-85f6-4f9c-b911-f2e912a5cc9a</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2016 06:52:54 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>